{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Custom Furniture Makers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/2102384/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":2102384,"taskName":"Furniture - Build Custom","taskDescription":"Build Custom Furniture","xmTaskDescriptor":"Custom Furniture Makers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":90,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Custom furniture patio outdoor wood","textMessagingName":"Custom Furniture","rolloverLongDesc":null,"rolloverShortDesc":"Includes tables, cabinets, sofas, desks, lighting, chairs, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build Custom Furniture.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Custom Furniture \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build Custom Wood, Bedroom \u0026 Living Room Furniture","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":35,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Custom Furniture","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Furniture - Build Custom","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Custom Furniture Builder Need","urlName":"Furniture-Build-Custom","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Custom Furniture Makers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdisor | Wood, Bedroom \u0026 Living Room Furniture","searchKeywords":"furniture,patio,outdoor,wood,handmade,designer,builder, bookshelfs, book, shelves, bookshelves","emcCategoryOid":-12035,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":803,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/2102384/":{"taskOID":2102384,"originalTaskOID":2102384,"setID":803,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5810,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Furniture","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of furniture are you looking for? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1927,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dining table","answerDisplayText":"Dining table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2213,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"End table","answerDisplayText":"End table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1008,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedside table","answerDisplayText":"Bedside table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3789,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Media armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Media armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1957,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Display armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Display armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1019,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bench","answerDisplayText":"Bench","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1322,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chair","answerDisplayText":"Chair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5846,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sofa","answerDisplayText":"Sofa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6111,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Stool","answerDisplayText":"Stool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1891,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Desk","answerDisplayText":"Desk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1002,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Bed","answerDisplayText":"Bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5636,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5812,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What sort of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7214,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","answerDisplayText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7215,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"professional drawings","answerDisplayText":"professional drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5645,"questionDisplayText":"Expected Level of Quality","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of craftsmanship and materials do you expect?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2829,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","answerDisplayText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3886,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","answerDisplayText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","answerDisplayText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5810,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Furniture","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of furniture are you looking for? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1927,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dining table","answerDisplayText":"Dining table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2213,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"End table","answerDisplayText":"End table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1008,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedside table","answerDisplayText":"Bedside table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3789,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Media armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Media armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1957,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Display armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Display armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1019,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bench","answerDisplayText":"Bench","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1322,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chair","answerDisplayText":"Chair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5846,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sofa","answerDisplayText":"Sofa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6111,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Stool","answerDisplayText":"Stool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1891,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Desk","answerDisplayText":"Desk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1002,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Bed","answerDisplayText":"Bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5636,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1927,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dining table","answerDisplayText":"Dining table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2213,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"End table","answerDisplayText":"End table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1008,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedside table","answerDisplayText":"Bedside table","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3789,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Media armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Media armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1957,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Display armoire / cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Display armoire / cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1019,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bench","answerDisplayText":"Bench","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1322,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chair","answerDisplayText":"Chair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5846,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sofa","answerDisplayText":"Sofa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6111,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Stool","answerDisplayText":"Stool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1891,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Desk","answerDisplayText":"Desk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1002,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Bed","answerDisplayText":"Bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5636,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5812,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What sort of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7214,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","answerDisplayText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7215,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"professional drawings","answerDisplayText":"professional drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7214,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","answerDisplayText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7215,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"professional drawings","answerDisplayText":"professional drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5645,"questionDisplayText":"Expected Level of Quality","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of craftsmanship and materials do you expect?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2829,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","answerDisplayText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3886,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","answerDisplayText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","answerDisplayText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2829,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","answerDisplayText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3886,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","answerDisplayText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","answerDisplayText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}